homedit.com 2019-10-12

# Privacy Policy and Disclosure - Home Decorating Trends - Homedit

At Homedit.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.homedit.com and how it is used.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, Homedit.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## What Is A Cookie?

A cookie is a small text file (often including a unique identifier), that is sent to a user’s browser from a website’s computers and stored on a user’s computer’s hard drive or on a tablet or mobile device (collectively, “ **Computer** ”). A Cookie stores a small amount of data on your Computer about your visit to the Site.

We may also use “web beacons” (also known as “clear GIFs” or “pixel tags”) or similar technologies on our Site to enable us to know whether you have visited a web page or received a message. A web beacon is typically a one-pixel, transparent image (although it can be a visible image as well), located on a web page  which is retrieved from a remote website on the internet enabling the verification of an individual’s viewing or receipt of a web page or message. A web beacon helps us to understand whether you came to our website from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website, measure successes of email marketing campaigns and improve our website performance.

We place and access Cookies on your Computer; these Cookies are known as “first-party Cookies.” Cookies may also be placed and accessed by some of our third-party vendors, which are known as “third-party Cookies” and are described below. Some Cookies are “session Cookies,” which means that they are temporary Cookies that are only stored on your device while you are visiting our Site. Other Cookies are “persistent Cookies,” which means that they are stored on your device for a period of time after you leave our Site.

You can choose whether to accept Cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you disable this function (or keep this function disabled, as set by default by certain browsers), your experience on the Site may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

Information about the procedure to follow in order to enable or disable Cookies can be found at:

For more information about other commonly used browsers, please refer to <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/>.

### WordPress Cookies

WordPress uses cookies, or tiny pieces of information stored on your computer, to verify who you are. There are cookies for logged in users and for commenters – read more [here](https://codex.wordpress.org/WordPress_Cookies).

### Analytics Cookies

On this website, the controller has integrated the component of Google Analytics (with the anonymizer function). Google Analytics is a web analytics service. Web analytics is the collection, gathering, and analysis of data about the behavior of visitors to websites. A web analysis service collects, inter alia, data about the website from which a person has come (the so-called referrer), which sub-pages were visited, or how often and for what duration a sub-page was viewed. Web analytics are mainly used for the optimization of a website and in order to carry out a cost-benefit analysis of Internet advertising.

The operator of the Google Analytics component is Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, United States.

Google Analytics collect information about your use of the Site, and enable us to improve the way it works. For example, Google Analytics show us which are the most frequently visited pages on the Site, help us record any difficulties you have with the Site, and show us whether our advertising is effective or not.

We use Google Analytics, which collects anonymous data for us to better serve you with both better website design and content.

  *  **What Google Analytics features do we use?**  Please see the feature list for Google Analytics at <http://www.google.com/analytics/features>.
  *  **What do we do with your data?**  All tracking information is used to help better design our content and web design to meet the needs of the customer and enhance the Service. All of our activity meets Google Analytics Terms of Service which can be found here. <http://www.google.com/analytics/terms>.
  *  **Opt out of Google Analytics:**  You can opt out of the anonymous data collected from Google Analytics by disabling cookies in your web browser for the Services. This will only block Google Analytics Data for us, and will not affect other websites. You can also opt out of all Google Analytics Tracking Data on the web by installing a browser plugin provided by Google. This can be found here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. The anonymous statistics we gather may be shared with a third party vendor to assist us with analyzing data, creating ads and web design. For more information about how Google uses data, visit <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners>.

### Advertising Cookies

Advertising Cookies are set to display targeted promotions or advertisements based upon your interests on the Site or to manage our advertising. These Cookies collect information about your activities on this Site and other websites to provide you targeted advertising.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Homedit.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Homedit.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL’s –

Google Adsense: [Privacy Policy Google](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html)  
Cookie-ul DoubleClick DART: [Privacy Policy](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx).

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include [Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html), [Primis](https://www.primis.tech/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/primisPrivacyPolicy2018.pdf), [GumGum](https://gumgum.com/privacy-policy/), [Sovrn](https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/).

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.homedit.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-partyad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Homedit.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.homedit.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

## Links to Other Sites

Homedit.com has links to partners, sources and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

## Disclosure

The mission of Homedit.com is simple: we want to help you discover, research, and select the best home products that meets your needs, desires, and budget. We are constantly updating reviews, doing new tests, and exploring new products to ensure our recommendations are always as accurate and helpful as possible. The information contained on Homedit is intended for informational and educational purposes only.

Homedit.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program,  ShareASale and other similar affiliate advertising programs which are designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to such affiliates’ websites such as Amazon.com. Sometimes we get a commission through purchases made through our links.

## Mailing list or newsletter.

On the website of the Homedit.com, users are given the opportunity to subscribe to our enterprise’s newsletter. The input mask used for this purpose determines what personal data are transmitted, as well as when the newsletter is ordered from the controller.

The Homedit.com informs its customers and business partners regularly by means of a newsletter about enterprise offers. The enterprise’s newsletter may only be received by the data subject if (1) the data subject has a valid e-mail address and (2) the data subject registers for the newsletter shipping. A confirmation e-mail will be sent to the e-mail address registered by a data subject for the first time for newsletter shipping, for legal reasons, in the double opt-in procedure. This confirmation e-mail is used to prove whether the owner of the e-mail address as the data subject is authorized to receive the newsletter.

During the registration for the newsletter, we also store the IP address of the computer system assigned by the Internet service provider (ISP) and used by the data subject at the time of the registration, as well as the date and time of the registration. The collection of this data is necessary in order to understand the (possible) misuse of the e-mail address of a data subject at a later date, and it therefore serves the aim of the legal protection of the controller.

The personal data collected as part of a registration for the newsletter will only be used to send our newsletter. In addition, subscribers to the newsletter may be informed by e-mail, as long as this is necessary for the operation of the newsletter service or a registration in question, as this could be the case in the event of modifications to the newsletter offer, or in the event of a change in technical circumstances. There will be no transfer of personal data collected by the newsletter service to third parties. The subscription to our newsletter may be terminated by the data subject at any time. The consent to the storage of personal data, which the data subject has given for shipping the newsletter, may be revoked at any time. For the purpose of revocation of consent, a corresponding link is found in each newsletter. It is also possible to unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time directly on the website of the controller, or to communicate this to the controller in a different way.

 **MailChimp (The Rocket Science Group, LLC.)**

MailChimp is an email address management and message sending service provided by The Rocket Science Group, LLC.

Personal Data collected: email address.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)

 **OptinMonster –  **[Privacy Policy](https://optinmonster.com/privacy/)

## 

Social media Cookies are used to enable you to share pages and content you find interesting on our Site through third-party social networking and other websites. These Cookies may also be used for advertising purposes.

  *  **Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter, Inc.)**

The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/privacy)

  *  **Facebook Like &Share button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)**

The Facebook Like&Share button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

  *  **Flipboard button**

The Flipboard button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Flipboard social network provided by Flipboard Corporation.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://about.flipboard.com/privacy/)

  *  **Google+ +1 button and social widgets (Google Inc.)**

The Google+ +1 button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Google+ social network provided by Google Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/)

  *  **Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets (Pinterest)**

The Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Pinterest platform provided by Pinterest Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy)

### WordPress Cookies

WordPress uses cookies, or tiny pieces of information stored on your computer, to verify who you are. There are cookies for logged in users and for commenters – read more [here](https://codex.wordpress.org/WordPress_Cookies).

### Embedded content

Articles on this site may include embedded YouTube content.Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. Check out the YouTube Privacy Policy [here](https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/7671399?hl=en).

### Links to Other Sites

 _www.homedit.com_ has links to partners, sources and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

### Mailing list or newsletter.

By registering on the mailing list or for the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning this Application. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to this Application.

 **MailChimp (The Rocket Science Group, LLC.)**

MailChimp is an email address management and message sending service provided by The Rocket Science Group, LLC.

Personal Data collected: email address.

Place of processing: US – [Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)

 **OptinMonster –  **[Privacy Policy](https://optinmonster.com/privacy/)

## Contact forms

The website of the Homedit.com contains information that enables a quick electronic contact to our enterprise, as well as direct communication with us, which also includes a general address of the so-called electronic mail (e-mail address). If a data subject contacts the controller by e-mail or via a contact form, the personal data transmitted by the data subject are automatically stored. Such personal data transmitted on a voluntary basis by a data subject to the data controller are stored for the purpose of processing or contacting the data subject. There is no transfer of this personal data to third parties.

## Restriction of Liability

Homedit.com makes no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this website and expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this website.

No warranty of any kind, implied, expressed or statutory, including but not limited to the warranties of non-infringement of third party rights, title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and freedom from computer virus, is given with respect to the contents of this website or its hyperlinks to other Internet resources.

Reference in this website to any specific commercial products, processes, or services, or the use of any trade, firm or corporation name is for the information and convenience of the public, and does not constitute endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by Homedit.com

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and if we do we’ll post any changes on this page. If you continue to use the Services after those changes are in effect, you agree to the revised Privacy Policy. If the changes are significant, we may provide more prominent notice or get your consent as required by law.

## Contacting Us

If you have any requests concerning your personal information or other inquiries regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us by e-mail at _admin@homedit.com._
